in this tutorial we'll be going over how
在本教程中，我们将介绍如何
you can trace pixel art from images
您可以从图像中跟踪像素艺术
using inkscape now there is a built-in
使用Inkscape现在有一个内置的
feature for auto tracing your pixel art
自动跟踪您的像素艺术的功能
but it doesn't always produce the
但它并不总是产生
desired results in these instances it
在这些情况下所需的结果是
would be good to know how to trace pixel
如果知道如何跟踪像素会很好
art manually which we'll be going over
手工制作的艺术，我们将对其进行检查
in today's tutorial
在今天的教程中
[Music]
[音乐]
so getting us started here in inkscape
所以让我们从Inkscape开始
the first thing you'll want to do is
您要做的第一件事是
import the graphic that you'd like to
导入您想要的图形
trace over into inkscape as you can see
如你所见，追溯到Inkscape
that i've done here now for this
我现在所做的一切都是为了这个
demonstration i will be using this
演示我将使用这个
vector illustration of a fox that i
一只狐狸的矢量插图，我
downloaded from 123rf.com
从123rf.com下载
so once you have your graphic imported
因此，一旦您导入了图形
let's turn on the grid let's come up
让我们打开电网，让我们上来吧
here to where it says view
从这里到它所说的视线
and where it says page grid go ahead and
它说页面网格在哪里继续并
select that
选择那个
now by default your grid should be one
现在，默认情况下，您的格网应为
pixel by one pixel in size but we can
一个像素一个像素的大小，但我们可以
ensure that by going to document
通过转到文档来确保
properties so let's come up here to file
属性，所以让我们来这里归档
and go to document properties
并转到文档属性
and then come over here to the
然后到这里来
grids tab
栅格选项卡
and then down here where it says spacing
然后在这里，这里写着间距
x and spacing y it should be one and one
X和间距y应该是一加一
by default if yours isn't one and one go
默认情况下，如果您的不是一次性的
ahead and change that so that your grid
并改变这一点，这样你的网格
is spaced out one pixel by one pixel and
是由一个像素隔开的，并且
the end result of that if you zoom in
如果你放大它，最终的结果是
i'm going to hold ctrl and roll up my
我要按住Ctrl键并卷起我的
mouse wheel if you zoom in you can see
鼠标滚轮如果你放大你可以看到
all of the individual pixels represented
表示的所有单个像素
by these grid lines here we're going to
通过这些网格线，我们将
use these grid lines as a reference for
使用这些网格线作为参考
tracing over our image so let me zoom
在我们的图像上进行跟踪，让我放大
back out here
回到这里来
what i want to do now is take my graphic
我现在想做的就是把我的图片
and scale it down really small i want to
缩小到非常小的规模，我想
scale it down so small that one pixel
缩小到如此之小，以至于一个像素
squares that will will seem large in
将会看起来很大的正方形
comparison to it so i'm going to grab
比较一下，所以我要去拿
the transformation handle here i'm going
我要说的是这里的变形句柄
to hold control on my keyboard to lock
按住键盘上的控制键锁定
the proportions and i'm going to scale
比例，我要把比例
this down pretty small maybe down to
这是相当小的，也许可以降到
like um
就像这个
i don't know 150 pixels wide and you
我不知道150像素宽和你
could see what the width is while you're
可以看到宽度是多少，当你在
scaling by referencing the toolbar the
通过引用工具栏进行缩放
tool settings menu towards the top of
位于顶部的工具设置菜单
the screen so i'm going to set mine
屏幕，所以我要设置我的
right at about 150 and that that right
就在150左右，就是那个权利
there looks good now let me zoom in on
现在看起来很好，让我放大看
this
这
as you can see these individual squares
如你所见，这些单独的方块
here we're going to create boxes that
在这里，我们要创建的盒子
fill these squares
填满这些方块
in the color of the graphic beneath it
用它下面的图形的颜色
and then it's going to create like a
然后它就会创造出一个
pixel effect beneath it so let me just
它下面的像素效果，所以让我
reposition this a little bit i want this
稍微调整一下位置，我想要这个
i want the tip of the fox's nose here up
我要狐狸的鼻尖朝上
against this square grid line
在这条正方形网格线上
there we go so now let's go ahead and
好了，现在让我们继续前进，
create our initial box what we want to
创建我们想要的初始盒子
do first is enable snapping which is up
首先要做的是启用处于打开状态的捕捉
here this little magnet icon turn that
在这里，这个小磁铁图标转动那个
on and then from this drop down menu
打开，然后从该下拉菜单
where it says uh bounding boxes and
上面写着，呃，包围盒和
nodes we want those two enabled but we
我们希望启用这两个节点，但我们
don't want alignment enabled that's the
不希望启用对齐，这是
settings we want right now
我们现在需要的设置
so i'm going to grab my rectangle tool
所以我要拿起我的矩形工具
and i'm just going to click and drag
我只需点击并拖动
like this to create a box it should snap
像这样创建一个它应该折断的盒子
to the grid lines nice and evenly as you
到网格线，像你一样细腻而均匀
saw here and once you've done that you
在这里看到了，一旦你做到了，你就
can disable the node setting in the uh
可以禁用UM中的节点设置
snapping options we're going to leave
快照选项，我们将离开
we're going to leave bounding boxes
我们将保留包围盒
enabled but for the rest of this
已启用，但对于其余部分
tutorial we're going to leave these two
教程，我们将把这两个
disabled and now i'm going to take this
残障人士，现在我要拿着这个
i'm going to grab my dropper i'm going
我要去拿我的滴管我要走了
to make this the same color as the fox's
使它与狐狸的颜色相同
nose like that and now i'll grab my
像这样的鼻子，现在我要抓起我的
selection tool and i'll just snap that
选择工具，我只需要抓拍它
in there like that
在那里就像这样
let me zoom in a little bit now to
现在让我稍微放大一下，
duplicate that i'm going to press ctrl d
复制一份，我要按Ctrld
on the keyboard and i'm going to move
在键盘上，我要移动
this copy over here
这份副本在这里
and if you want to stamp copies while
如果您想在打印副本的同时
you're doing this you could just hold
你在做这件事你可以按住
the click and then press the space bar
单击，然后按空格键
and it'll stamp a copy like that and
它会像这样盖上一份复印件
i'll put another one down here for the
我会把另一个放在这里
fox's nose like that and i'll just leave
狐狸那样的鼻子，我就走了
that one there
那边的那个
okay so now i'm going to duplicate this
好的，现在我要复制这个
again i'm going to press ctrl d to
我再一次按下ctrl d键
duplicate this i want to make this one
复制这个，我想做这个。
the same color as this shade right here
和这里的这个颜色一样的颜色
so i'm going to grab my dropper again
所以我要再次拿起我的滴管
and go like that and there we go now we
就这样走了，现在我们走了，我们
have that box and i'm just going to
有了那个盒子，我就去
stamp that in there and try to follow
在那里盖上印记，然后试着跟着
along the lines of the subject here
沿着这个主题的脉络
although it's not going to be exactly
尽管它不会完全是
precise
精确
what you're going for is a close
你想要的是一个结束
representation it's not going to be
代表它不会是
exact but if you just follow along um in
完全正确，但如果你只是跟着，嗯，
a rudimentary way it should look good
一种基本的方式应该看起来很好
once you're finished and zoomed out
一旦你完成并缩小了
okay so let me put these over here
好的，让我把这些放在这里
and again to stamp these copies i'm just
再说一次，为了在这些副本上盖章，我只是
pressing the spacebar
按空格键
on my keyboard to do that
在我的键盘上做到这一点
now if you notice here it's hard to see
现在如果你注意到这里很难看到
what's actually going on so what i would
到底发生了什么，所以我会
recommend doing is clicking on the image
推荐的做法是点击图片
and reducing the opacity of it i'm going
减少它的不透明度，我要去
to open up the fill and stroke menu
打开填充和描边菜单的步骤
which is located over here
它位于这里
and over here where it says opacity i'm
在这里，它写着不透明，我是
going to bring that down
我要把这一点降下来
and i would even recommend making the
我甚至会建议把
page darker than white so that you can
比白色更暗的页面，这样你就可以
see the white boxes when we start
当我们开始时看到白色方框
creating them so i'm going to come back
创造它们，这样我就会回来
to the document properties tab and come
转到文档属性选项卡，然后进入
over here to the display tab and where
在这里到Display(显示)选项卡，在哪里
it says page i'm going to click on that
上面写着我要点击这个页面
and i'm going to make that a darker
我要把它变得更黑暗
shade i'm going to make that maybe
遮阳板，也许我会把它做出来
something like gray so we can see a
像灰色这样的东西，所以我们可以看到
little better
好一点
okay so let me zoom back in here
好的，让我把这里放大
let me uh create some more boxes
让我，呃，再创建一些盒子
to fill in my subject here
在这里填写我的主题
i'm going to create the ear right here
我要在这里创建耳朵
and use this color so let me bring the
用这个颜色，所以让我带上
opacity of this image back up so i can
备份此图像的不透明度，以便我可以
sample a better so i can sample that
试一件更好的，这样我就可以试一试了
color properly properly back to the fill
正确地将颜色调回填充物
and stroke menu with the image selected
和选中图像的笔划菜单
bring the opacity all the way up there
把不透明度一直带到那里
we go
我们走吧
and let me create a duplicate of this
让我来创建一个副本
box right here to move the page around
选中此处框可在页面周围移动
i'm just pressing down the mouse wheel
我只是按下鼠标滚轮
and moving the mouse let me take this
移动鼠标让我拿到这个
one duplicate that by pressing ctrl d
按下ctrl d即可重复此操作
and i'll make this a darker shade let me
我会把它改成更深的色调让我
grab my dropper tool right here
抓住我的滴管工具就在这里
make that a darker shade like that and i
把它变成像那样的深色，我就会
may even change these boxes right here
甚至可以在这里改变这些方框
to be the same color
是同一种颜色
just for consistency
只是为了保持一致性
okay that's a nice contrasting shade
好的，这个色调对比很好。
compared to the other orange so i'm
与另一个橙色相比，所以我
going to leave that as it is
我会让它保持原样
let me make copies in here again just
让我在这里再复印一次
pressing the space bar to stamp copies
按空格键可为副本加盖印记
there we go
好了，我们走吧
i'll put some copies up here
我会在这里放一些复印件
for this part of the ear
对于耳朵的这一部分
there we go
好了，我们走吧
now i'm not what i'm doing right here is
现在我不是，我现在要做的是
i'm not filling in the entire subject
我不会把整个题目都填进去
i'm just creating like an outline around
我只是在创造一个大概的轮廓
the main areas let me turn the opacity
主要区域让我将不透明度
of that image back down so i can see a
这样我就可以看到一个
little better there we go we want to try
我们做得更好，我们想试一试
not to make duplicate copies of squares
不要复制正方形的副本
in those grid lines if possible
如果可能的话，在这些网格线上
there we go
好了，我们走吧
let me just make an outline here going
让我在这里做一个提纲
around the outline of the shading
围绕着着色的轮廓
okay looking good
好的，看起来不错
do this one as well
把这件也做好
and don't worry about it being exactly
不要担心它是不是
flush with the uh boundaries of the
与呃边界齐平的
subject it's not gonna be perfect but
主题不会是完美的，但
that's okay it doesn't have to be
没关系，不一定非得这样
perfect so let me fill this in a little
太好了，让我稍微填一下
more
更多
okay now i'm gonna fill in the ear up
好了，现在我要填满耳朵了
here using these colors again ctrl d to
在这里再次使用这些颜色ctrl d to
duplicate and then just click and drag
复制，然后只需单击并拖动
and press down the space bar to stamp
然后按下空格键即可盖章
copies of it as you see me doing here
就像你看到我在这里做的那样
okay so now i'm going to start filling
好的，现在我要开始填充
in the white area here and this is where
在这里的白色区域，这就是
you'll see why it is that i change the
您将看到为什么我要更改
page border or the page color rather
页面边框或页面颜色
because it makes it easier to see the
因为这样可以更容易地看到
white i'm going to make that box white
我要把那个盒子变成白色
and now you can see it much easier up
现在你可以更容易地看到它了
against that backdrop there you can see
在那里的背景下，你可以看到
exactly where the white boxes or pixels
白色方框或像素的确切位置
as they're supposed to be are being
就像他们应该做的那样
placed
安放
and a little shortcut for filling in
还有一条填写信息的快捷方式
these large areas you don't have to
这些面积很大的区域你不必
create individual boxes for each of
为每个选项创建单独的框
these areas you can just take one of
这些区域你可以只取其中一个
these transformation handles and bring
这些转换句柄和带来
it down like that and as you can see it
它就这样落了下来，正如你所看到的
just fills in the whole area nice and
只是填满了整个区域，很漂亮
easily without having to create too many
轻松实现，无需创建太多
other copies in fact you could take
其他的复印件，事实上你可以
these existing copies right there and
这些现有的副本就在那里
just fill them in like that as you can
尽你所能像这样填写就行了
see there okay so if i if i zoom out a
看这里，好的，如果我缩小一个
little bit you can see this thing is
你可以看到这个东西是
starting to come together you could
开始走到一起，你可以
actually take the original image and
实际上取走原始图像，
press delete to get rid of it just to
按Delete将其删除，只是为了
give you a temporary look at how it's
让你暂时看看它是如何
coming along now if you want to get your
现在就来如果你想让你的
image back just just do an undo which is
映像返回只需撤消即可
ctrl z
Ctrl z键
ctrl z on the keyboard undoes your last
键盘上的Ctrl z键可以撤消您的上一次操作
action so it puts it back there and now
行动，所以现在就把它放回原处
i'm just gonna go and fill in this part
我要去填一下这部分
of the shading of the subject here using
在这里使用对象的阴影
these darker
这些颜色更深一些
boxes okay so now that that's filled in
箱子好了，现在已经填好了
i'm going to fill in this area over here
我要把这块填在这里
this part of the darker shading as well
这部分也是较暗的阴影
okay so as you can see here it's
好的，如你所见，这是
starting to come along nicely if i
开始变得很好了，如果我
delete this you can see it's starting to
删除这个，你可以看到它开始
come together a little bit still got a a
稍微聚一聚，还是得了a
ways to go here i think what i'll do
去这里的路我想我要做的是
next is i'll fill in this lighter area i
下一步，我将填写这个较浅的区域
guess this reflection of light on the
我猜这是光线反射在
fox's back right here
福克斯就在这里
okay so next up i will fill in the tail
好的，接下来我来填一下尾巴
here these three different areas of the
在这里，这三个不同的领域
tail and then i will fill in the larger
尾巴，然后我会填写较大的
part of the body and then we will be
身体的一部分，然后我们就会
finished
完工了
[Music]
[音乐]
okay so i'm pretty much finished here i
好了，我差不多说完了
just have to fill in this large area
只需填写这一大片区域
right here which i could fill in by
就在这里，我可以填上
creating individual boxes but it would
创建单独的框，但它会
be pretty tedious so what i'm going to
相当乏味，所以我要做的是
do is i'm going to take a little bit of
我要做的是，我要拿一点
a shortcut here and use the bezier pen
这里的快捷方式并使用Bezier钢笔
to just manually draw a shape and fill
手动绘制形状和填充的步骤
it in with the color that would
它与它的颜色很相配
otherwise be filled here so let me turn
否则在这里被填满，所以让我转身
off my snapping to do that i'm going to
离开我的抓拍去做我要做的
grab the bezier pen and this is a trick
抓起贝塞尔钢笔，这是一个骗局
you may want to employ yourself
你可能想雇佣你自己
depending on the image you're working
取决于您正在处理的图像
with if it has large areas of a single
如果它有大片的单一区域
color like this
像这样的颜色
you may want to do something like this
您可能想做这样的事情
yourself so let me grab the bezier pen
你自己，我去拿贝塞尔钢笔
over here keyboard shortcut is b let me
在这里，键盘快捷键是b让我
zoom in on this
放大这张图
and i'm just going to draw a shape going
我只想画一个形状
through the edges here that i'm going to
穿过这里的边缘，我要
use to fill in the rest of this object
用于填充此对象的其余部分
and then we will be finished
然后我们就完事了
so let me just uh
所以让我只是呃
come around the edges here like this
像这样绕过这里的边缘
there we go
好了，我们走吧
back to the starting point
回到起点
and i will make this the same color
我会把这个做成同样的颜色
as the object that i'd like to the boxes
作为我想要的箱子里的物品
i would have filled in there otherwise
要不然我就填进去了
and i can get rid of that outline by
我可以通过以下方式摆脱这个轮廓
holding shift
按住班次
and clicking on this little x down here
然后点击下面这个小x
now i'm going to take this grab this
现在我要拿着这个拿着这个
selection tool i'm going to send that to
选择工具，我将把它发送到
the bottom using this button right here
底部用这里的这个按钮
lower selection to the bottom
将选区降低到底部
and then i'm going to raise it one step
然后我要把它提高一步
by uh clicking this button next to it
通过点击它旁边的这个按钮
that says
那是说
or two buttons over to the left that
或左边的两个按钮，
says raise selection one step and now it
说提高选择一步，现在就是
should be over the original image now
现在应该已经超过了原始图像
let me zoom out a little bit
让我把镜头缩小一点
let me take the original image and move
让我拿着原始图像，然后移动
it out of the way
别挡道了
as you can see here we're pretty much
如你所见，我们基本上
finished we have our vector
完成后，我们有了我们的矢量
pixel art that we created from the
创建的像素艺术。
vector fox here
这里是媒介狐狸
now if i zoom out one more thing i
现在，如果我再放大一件事，我
wanted to point out let's turn off the
我想指出的是，让我们关掉
page grid i'm going to come up here to
页面网格，我要到这里来
where it says view
上面写着查看的地方
where it says page grid i'm going to
上面写着我要去的页面网格
deselect that
取消选择该选项
now if you notice
现在如果你注意到
there's space showing through
有空间可以看得出来
these boxes in here
这些箱子在这里
because of the way vector graphics work
由于矢量图形的工作方式
in general this isn't just an
总的来说，这不仅仅是一个
inkscape problem this happens in every
Inkscape问题这发生在每个
vector application you're going to
您将使用向量应用程序
notice these little these little gaps
注意这些小小的缝隙
between the boxes here maybe it's not so
在这里的盒子之间，也许不是这样的
apparent on my screen if i were to make
在我的屏幕上很明显，如果我
this page background a little darker
这个页面的背景稍微暗了一点
you'd probably see it you can see more
你可能会看到它，你会看到更多
of those
在那些人中
um lines showing through between the
嗯，穿透的线
boxes the way that we remedy this is
我们补救这个问题的方法是
just by selecting everything and
仅仅通过选择一切和
duplicating it so let me select
复制它，让我选择
everything here
这里的一切
i actually want to select everything
我真的想选择所有的东西
except for this large image in here or
除了这里的这张大图
this large object that i drew with the
我画的这个大物件
bezier pen so to deselect just that part
Bezier钢笔，以取消选择该部分
i'm going to hold shift and click on
我要按住Shift键并单击
that to deselect it and now i should
取消选择它，现在我应该
just have the boxes selected and with
只需选中这些框并使用
the boxes selected you can duplicate
您可以复制选定的框
them by pressing ctrl d on the keyboard
通过按键盘上的ctrl d键
and there you go if you zoom out those
如果你把它们缩小，你就能看到了
uh gaps should be gone if they're not
呃，如果没有的话，差距应该消失了
you could just duplicate it one more
你只要再复制一个就行了
time and that should do the trick
时间，这应该会奏效的
and there you go that is how
就是这样，这就是为什么
you can fix that problem
你可以解决这个问题
and i think that should do it for this
我认为这应该可以解决这个问题
tutorial that is how you can go about
教程，这就是你可以如何去做
creating uh simple pixel art tracings
创建，呃，简单的像素艺术痕迹
over vector graphics using inkscape if
使用Inkscape IF覆盖矢量图形
you found this lesson useful then
你觉得这一课很有用吗？
consider checking out my inkscape master
考虑一下我的Inkscape大师
class it's a collection of over 60
班级它是一个超过60个人的集合
videos where i go over all of the tools
我浏览了所有工具的视频
and features in inkscape and i explain
和Inkscape中的功能，我解释
what they are and demonstrate how they
它们是什么并演示它们如何
work kind of like how i did in this
就像我在这件事上做的那样
video we even have a private community
视频我们甚至有一个私人社区
where you can ask questions and get help
在这里您可以提出问题并获得帮助
from me anytime you want and best of all
在你想要的任何时候从我这里，最好的是
there's no monthly membership fees you
没有每月会员费
just pay 17
只需支付17
one time and you're in for life i'll
一次，你就会终身监禁，我会
have some information about that down
有一些相关信息
below if you want to check that out as
如果您想检查一下，请在下面作为
always thanks for watching
始终感谢观看
[Music]
[音乐]
you
你